Md Farhad

House #3, Road #8, Block #E, Section 12, Mirpur, Dhaka | 01960-918062 | farhad45203@gmail.com | https://github.com/farhad45203



OBJECTIVE

I am a qualified Front End Web Developer with 4+ years of experience. Strong creative and analytical skills and I try to learn something new day by day. I can provide you with any type of design to build a website using HTML, CSS or frameworks like React JS or Next JS.

COMPUTER SKILLS

MS Word, Excel, HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Java, Wordpress, React js, Next js and React Native.

EXPERIENCE

Dates 2020-Present	Front End Web Developer, SOCIAN LIMITED • The development of the front end depends on the project of the company.
Dates 2018-2020	 Data Entry Operator, SOCIAN LIMITED Data processing, data analysis and data management according to the needs of the company.
Education	
Dates	Bachelor of Social Science Dhaka Mirnur Goyt Bangahandhu College

Dates Running	Bachelor of Social Science, Dhaka Mirpur, Govt. Bangabandhu College.
Dates 2018-2020	Higher Secondary School, Dhaka Mirpur, Govt. Bangabandhu College.

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

Confident, articulate, and professional speaking abilities.

Empathic listener.

Writing creative or factual.

Honesty and loyalty.

Excellent presentation and negotiation skills.

PROJECT INFO

I have created multiple projects using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery and JavaScript for practice and learning purposes. I have created some more front-end projects for office purposes. Like Pandit app, Pandit web, Sive web, Chikitsa app, Chikitsa website, Qped app and also socian.ai website, evanmandery.com a portfolio website etc, using HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript, React js, Next js, React Native also uses Java.

PROJECTS EXAMPLE

miPos - A Ticket selling fully responsive landing page Technology used HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

https://farhad45203.github.io/miPos/

Evan Mandery - A portfolio website fully responsive and dynamic Technology used React js, CSS, HTML

http://evanmandery.com/

For more - This is my portfolio

Technology used Next js, Tailwind CSS, HTML

https://farhad-one.vercel.app/